Ending
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen.
We are the three sisters of Yakiniku.
I'm Yoda.
I'm Kaene.
I'm Tazuki.
This is Ame.
It's so cold!
You're wearing a nice T-shirt.
Yes, I am.
I'll introduce you later.
See you later.
Let's go.
A barbecue restaurant.
Wait.
Here.
This way.
Here we go.
Daisies!
Hi!
Look.
This way.This way.
This is Mr. Shinkaen.
I've always wanted to come.
I'm hungry.
It's morning.
Let's eat.
For breakfast.
Of course I'm hungry.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Hello. - Hello.
There's someone here to see you.
Yes, please.
Hello, sir.
Ta-da!
Yoo-hoo!
Price
What price is this?
Suddenly it's vertical.
Did you have breakfast?
I didn't eat breakfast.
You just woke up.
Did you eat?
A little.
Natto.
Rice.
I ate rice.I've been eating rice.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
What did I order?
We haven't ordered anything yet.
No, no, no.
Please.
We're choosing enews.
Tongue and belly.
Can I order?
Yes, you may order.
Do you have yukke?
We don't have yukke right now.
I see.
We grill them yukke style.
Ah...
Okay, then.
Two.
Yes, sir.
Tongue.
There are different kinds of tongue.
Where's the tongue?
This one is the best.
The outside is fine.
You don't mind if I eat it?
You like it?
I love it. I love it.
Can we? If you can.
No, maybe not the whole thing.No, maybe not the whole thing.
Who can gobble it up.
Let's do it later.
Let's do it now.
PokerFain.
Oh, yeah.
Rice eater.
Give me a bite.
All right.
Shaw.
Two Shaw.
Can I have a show show from two shows?
Mister...
Omonnan
Order Complete
Done
I'm looking forward to it.
I didn't hear anything about the order.
You two are playing with each other.
I'm sorry.
I was just wondering if you guys could eat this lemon and put on a poker face and just nibble on it.
Let's do it.
I want to do it later.
I bet Momocho eats lemons, doesn't she?
He eats them like they're oranges.
Even when the waiter clears away the empty plate, she leaves something behind.I don't know what it is, but even when the waiter clears the empty plate, he always leaves something behind.
At first I wondered why they left it.
He eats lemon!
It's amazing.
Do you want a squeeze?
Maybe I'll squeeze it.
I'm gonna squeeze some lemons.
Lemon squeezer.
You look good squeezing lemons.
Thank you very much.
I don't know what to thank you for.
I'll save some for you to eat.
Lemon squeezer.
I haven't had a lemon in like five years.
I haven't even bitten into a lemon.
Even the smell.
It smells bad.
Oh, man.
Here we go.
Okay.
It's good.
Yeah, it's good.
Are we losing?
Losing?
I don't know. The judges are watching us now.
I'm totally fine with it.
I'm out of here.I'm off!
It's Jotanshio!
Wow, it looks delicious!
It's salty, so you can share it with lemon.
Please be careful, it burns easily.
Let's grill it.
Let's start with the Jotan salt.
Yes, Kamitan salt.
It's nice.
It's amazing. It's gorgeous.
How is it?
Looks delicious!
This tan.
It's magnificent
It's a magnificent tan
It's a magnificent tan.
Shinoshita.
Well then...
I'd like to grill it.
The salt sauce looks delicious.
Looks good.
Sounds good.
what was it ASMR?
ASMR
can you hear it?
Ear down.
Uh, on the mic.Oh, by Mike.
Mike Mike.
Hot, hot, hot.
Hot face.
Okay, I'm going to grill three.
Okay, thank you very much.
I'm hungry.
Wow, that looks good. I love morning roast.
Is it well done? Not so bad.
I don't know if I'm a good griller. I'm a good griller. Me too.
What was that? Well done.
What? Like, super well-done?
You mean burnt?
Rare is half-baked?
Half raw.
What's rarer than rare? Very rare?
I don't know.
I don't know... - You're speaking Japanese.
Looks delicious. Maybe I'll go there too.
Green salad, sir. Wow.
That's great. I can go too.
I'm glad you have so many salads. I can go, too.
You want to go?
Yes, please.
If it's not cooked enough, do it again. Thank you.
Okay, what do we do?
What do we do?
I don't know.Yeah, it's good.
Is it good?
It's good.
It's so cute.
Bon appétit.
Isn't it good?
It's so good.
So cute, so cute, so cute.
Yummy, yummy, yummy.
How did you do that?
Don't take a picture of me with a smug look on your face.
You always get it on your face when you eat.
It's just the way it's made.
I put it on all the time.
I can't help it.
I love the belly, too.
What do you want me to say?
How do I say it?
I know, I know.
I know it so well.
It's huge.
I'm going to burn it.
Oh no, I'll be burned!
What the hell is that?
What's the setup today?
What kind of character?
Morning tension.
You want some food?You want some rice?
A little rice.
A little show rice, please.
I'll have some.
Yes, sir.
Mmm-hmm.
Thank you.
I've never heard that before.
You really have a sense of humor, don't you?
Is this yours?
Is the meat okay?
Can it be a little red?
Sure.
Yes, just in case.
Thank you.
Shall we eat?
Is that garlic?
Oh, my God, garlic.
Garlic, right?
Oh, my God.
I'm going to a meet and greet.
Shhh...
You're going to win?
I'm in.
Meat for the win?
I'm going to win and spread it!I'm going to win and spread it out.
You look okay.
We're good
Yes we're good
Stage technique.
Nogizaka's a little...
If they smell of garlic...
This one's fine.
Yeah, it's fine.
I'm fine.
Okay, then.
All of it. All of it.
All of it?
Yeah. - Okay.
I'll just put it on.
Oh, shit.
Let's try the halibut.
Put a lot of sauce on it.
Rice is here, too.
I love it.
Yum!
Looks so good!
I can't believe I just said that!
Ho, ho, ho!
I didn't say anything.
It's so good!
It looks so delicious!Looks so delicious!
Oh my God!
There's a place that serves great jalami.
Yes.
We always go there to eat halami.
It looks amazing!
Yes.
I want some.
Looks good.
Is it good?
It's delicious.
It's so good!
Yumen-zou.
It's good.
Oh, man.
I feel like I made it.
I don't think I've heard of it before.
That's it.
Oh, man.
Oh, my gosh!
How's that?
Mmm!
Yum?
Yum!
I want some of this.
Tuna?You want some tuna?
First time?
This is a first.
First time for you?
That's great.
Tuna, please. First tuna.
Cut it open, please.
I'll do it!
You shook... for a second.
I was shaking.
Is it good?
Oh, my God.
You got over it.
It's delicious.
I thought I'd never make it.
Sushi is surprisingly good, too.
You're right.
It's even better than mine!
That's for sure.
Let's go to Kura Sushi together sometime.
Oh, I want to go with you.
Let's go?
I want to go, too.
Let's play Bicrapon.
I want to play "Bikurapon.
We're so into all kinds of stuff.
We love everything.I like anything.
Anything.
I wanted to say "anything.
Yes, we are "anything goes" people.
I like grilled meat.
Anything's fine.
I like yakiniku.
I want to go snowboarding.
Oh, snowboarding.
It all started with snowboarding, right?
That's right, ladies and gentlemen, we were originally three snowboarding sisters.
Yeah.
I've never even tried it.
Right.
Three sisters who want to snowboard
Yes, three sisters who want to go snowboarding
That's why you formed the group, right?
Yes, that's why we have to go skiing or snowboarding, which is the origin of the group.
That's right.
We want to go snowboarding and get hungry and eat meat!
That's great!
You don't want to eat meat in the snow?
Medicine?
Oh, yeah, that's a good idea.
You're not going to freeze?
Not freezing?
Oh, no, we should bring a charcoal stove.Oh, no, you're bringing a shichirin!
I'll take the shichirin.
I'll get the charcoal.
Bring the charcoal.
Bring the charcoal, okay.
I mean, yukkis, yukkis like seared yukkis.
Mix them together.
Let's mix it.
Okay, I'll mix it.
I'll mix it.
Shall I take it out?
Oh, mix it up.
You must be the camera.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I can't wait to put it on.
Put it on, put it on.
Yeah, put it on.
Put it on.
Eat it.
How is it? Is it good?
Yeah, it's really good.
You don't mind? Eat it.
Yeah, go ahead, eat it.
Bon appétit, seared yukkis.
Here you go.
Go ahead.
Here you go.Here you go.
Looks good!
What kind of sauce is this?
Salt?
Egg?
It's so good! Eat up!
Wow!
This is so good!
Isn't this visual amazing?
I love the visual!
Is it good?
It's so good!
Bon appétit!
Is it good?
It's kind of sweet.
It's delicious.
I want you to try it.
Bon appétit.
It's a loin, isn't it?
It's good, isn't it?
Are you okay?
Let me see.
It's cute.
You know... they gave me a different sauce for the yukaye.
They gave me a different one.
Oh!Aah!
Aah!
Hey, hey.
Like the guy with the fireball.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, that's not funny, is it?
Oh, no!
I didn't think Den was gonna bring it.
Me neither.
I'm glad you're laughing.
I'll get you an extra...
Roast.
I also eat rice with the meat.
It's the best!
Yes, sir.
How is it? Hot.
It's cute. It's good. It's good.
Good. Good, good, good.
I'll have the loin, please.
Oh, yeah! Looks delicious!
It's so lean!
Rice! Roll it in rice!
Oh! Looks so good!
It's so good!
How is it? Is it good?
Yummy!
What's with the T-shirt, ladies and gentlemen?What's this T-shirt, folks?
Buy it.
I'm not selling it.
Yoda made it for me.
Let's go, Icy.
It's getting cold. I'll make a sweatshirt turn.
I want one!
But wouldn't it be a good idea to sell them?
Sell it! I'm going to start a business.
Wouldn't it be cute to make a strap with grilled meat on it?
Let's make it!
I'll use the money from Yoda's sales to eat barbecued meat.
That's the best!
Yakiniku straps with your favorite part of the meat!
That's so cool!
It's so good!
Please buy the goods so that we can eat delicious Yakiniku!
Please, please, please!
I love it!
Which one is your favorite?
Of the day.
What did I eat?
Tampin and tarami.
Tongue?
Tongue.
Yukke.
Yukke.Yukke
What's good?
Eggplant? I don't know.
It was the best.
Oh, there you go.
I cried.
I'm crying, I'm crying, I'm crying.
I want the loin.
Loin.
You like roast.
You like red meat.
The roast is good.
It's good.
But I also like the tongue with the sauce.
I love it.
It's good.
It was good.
If it's tongue, can we go again?
I can do it.
You guys are amazing.
We're calling this place.
Sorry.
I haven't eaten yet.
I've already eaten one meal today.
I really mean it.
We came here with that kind of mindset.
We weren't prepared.
It's a difference in mindset.This kind of difference in mindset...
It's no good if there's a discrepancy.
It'll lead to a dissolution of the company
That's right, we're on the verge of breaking up.
So you have to be firm in that area.
I want you to be firm.
I understand.
Okay, you got it?
Lemon judgments.
Judgement.
Okay, that's fine.
Sorry, Lemon.
Forgive me.
Wait, there's no way our song is "Sorry, Lemon.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That part surprised me.
It's totally unrelated, but it sounds okay.
You're right.
And the rap song... you made an afterthought.
I'm over it.
Let's all just step on it and figure it out.
Let's think about it.
Wrap it up.
A few future numbers.
Okay.
A few future numbers.a few more in the future
Fewer in the future
a few in the future
Knitted tights for life
I'll wear knitted tights for the rest of my life when I get a hand trowel.
Will you wear knitted tights?
I'll wear them.
Remember?
Remember when you wore knitted tights?
I remember.
Not knitted tights, stockings.
You wore stockings on the sidewalk?
That picture's not good, is it?
Let me see. Let me see.
I'll show you later.
I've worn knitted tights in the past.
Why? Why?
At home. At home.
Why? Alone?
Before I went in, before I went in.
Why?
I don't know what kind of man you are.
Later.
Hmm.
Hey, we'll do this. We'll do this. We'll do this.
It's the end of the year.
It's on again.It's on again.
You're an idol, why don't you put whipped cream on it? That's the secret of being an idol, don't put yakiniku sauce on a day when you can go for a big drive.
After 8 years, I think it's a good idea.
Good girl.
????
Here they come.
Ahh...
ahhhhh...
interesting movie from here
Camera play 8 years of idol camera play
8 years and then they start fooling around
Sundup de sundup de sundup de sundup de sundup de sundup
Doob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob-dob!
You make it all the time, don't you, Deng-chan?
I want to compare.
You didn't bring it today?
No, not today.
What are you doing? Where are you sticking it?
I'll start here.
It's soooo warm!
Shall I heat it up?
It's not here today. It's just a coincidence it's not here.
Eggs
It's hot. I can't eat spicy food.
Is my sundop sweet?
No, it's not. Not too spicy.
I'll search for spicy.
I can have spicy food too.I can handle spicy food.
Taste? Taste, taste, taste.
Then we'll taste it ourselves.
Okay.
You two can do spicy?
Yes, but not too hot.
Wow, it's good.
It's so good!
It's spicy.
It's delicious.
Den-chan, it's almost too hot.
Too bad?
It's good, it's good.
But it's okay.
No, it's too spicy for me.
It's a pain in the ass.
It's good. It's better than where I live.
That's true.
Here we go. In between.
Now, the egg part.
Stand over here. Shine the light on it.
The light.
Okay, all done.
Delicious.
What's moving so fast?
Yum. Yum.
Looks good.Looks delicious!
I love the spiciness.
Really?
Which is better?
But is it yours?
Let's go eat.
This one, of course.
It's delicious.
Each one has its own merits.
I want to go eat.
Isn't it cute?
It's not cute!
Dendubu... please write it in Roman characters.
Today's menu
Recommended Ddeungdubu
Oh no, it's not cute!
Cool!
Haddub
Don't be embarrassed to say it.
I know.
It's delicious!
Delicious!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Okay, I'll have the blueberry.
Yes, I've already finished it.
It was delicious.
It was really good.
I want to go back.I'd love to go back.
Please let me know in the comments if you want to come back and if you have any other recommendations.
We'll be there.
And the meat, too!
Please wait for the second installment!
See you soon!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel and click the "Good" button!
Well, I hope everyone had a good time today.
It was delicious.
It was great.
Thanks again.
Let's go again.
We'll go again soon.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Come on, bye-bye.
Bye-bye.